YYeTs.com
人人影视
*Better pray for hell*
时间轴： 浓子   萌    校对： 苏小黛   胖兔纯
Forgive me.
原谅我
Have you lost your lust for life?
你对生活失去性趣了吗
Don't tell me that you are full up.
别告诉我你已经玩够了
Perhaps some holes cannot be filled.
或许是某个黑洞欲求不满
Really, my lord?
是吗  大人
Which holes are those?
那是什么洞啊
The ones we dig for ourselves.
那个我们为自己挖的洞
What weighs so heavy on you, love?
亲爱的  你的神情为何如此沉重
By the taste of it, my father's boot.
怕我父亲用鞋底抽我
You're a big boy now.
你现在是大人了
Grown men don't fear their fathers.
成熟男人可不怕他们的父亲
You don't know my father.
你又不认识我父亲
Everyone knows your father.
是个人都认识他
Precisely.
也对
No, you can't go in there!
不  你不能进去
Captain Alden!
奥登上尉
No! No! No!
不  不  不
Leave him alone!
放开他
Get out.
滚
This is how you wipe the innocent blood off your hands?
这就是你赎罪的方法吗
On the ass of a whore?
干得爽吗
Giles Corey never pled!
吉尔斯·科里从没为自己辩白过
Ergo, we don't know he was innocent!
所以我们如何得知他是清白的
Give me one good reason
给我一个
why I don't put you in the ground.
不杀你的理由
Sir, I cannot.
我说不出来
I've been expecting the angel of death since I was 10.
自我十岁起  我就期望死神的到来
I didn't see him myself, but I knew from the look
我没亲眼看到过他  但在我祖父临死前
in grandfather's eyes just before he went,
我在他的眼神里
the angel bore a most terrible face.
看到了死神恐怖的面孔
Quite like yours, I expect.
正如你现在这样
So come, angel.
动手吧  天使
You find me fully prepared
你会发现我已完全准备好
to burn like a human candle for eternity
成为一支人肉蜡烛  和所有那些该死的人一起
in a pit of burning black tar with all the other damned.
在燃烧着黑焦油的深渊里照亮永恒
Burning black tar?
燃烧的黑焦油
I thought hell was fire.
不应该是地狱火吗
A common misconception.
那是种普遍的错误观念
Hellfire burns like fire
地狱之火形态似火
But is the consistency of thick black pitch.
但其实是粘稠的黑沥青
What?
怎么了
What have you seen?
你看到什么了
Not sure.
不知道
Hell on earth, maybe.
可能是世间的地狱吧
Get dressed.
穿好衣服
I've got something to show you.
我有东西给你看
Where are we going?
这是去哪里
The woods.
树林
To what end?
去那里干什么
You have the moral compass of a meat ant,
虽然你道德败坏如同蝼蚁
but you do know something about witches.
但巫师的事你确实知道点
I saw them.
我看到过他们
Just like Mercy Lewis described them.
就跟梅西·路易丝描述的一样
Animal heads and all.
人体兽头之类的
Captain Alden.
奥登上尉
As magistrate of Salem, I hereby place you under arrest
作为塞勒姆的治安官  我以你昨晚
for violent remonstrations in the common last night.
在绞刑架下的暴力抗议罪逮捕你
You shall face charges of disorderly, riotous mischief
你将面临妨碍公共秩序
and incitement to mayhem.
和煽动混乱罪的起诉
Talk to Isaac. He'll show you the way.
去找艾萨克  他会带你去的
What are you gonna do, Hale?
你想怎样  霍尔
Press me to death just like you did to Giles Corey?
像逼死吉尔斯·科里一样把我逼死吗
I suggest you take that up with your new friend,
这该怪你的牧师新朋友吧
the reverend, as it was his doing, not mine.
都是他干的  与我无关
Away with him.
带他走
You've had a busy night.
你今晚够忙的啊
When were you planning to tell me you'd arrested John Alden?
你打算什么时候告诉我你逮捕了约翰·奥登
Before or after you hang him?
把他绞死前还是绞死后呢
The man is a loose canon.
他就是个不定时炸弹
He threatened the selectmen in front of half the town.
他在全镇一半的人面前公然威胁镇长
If he's a problem, he's my problem.
如果他是个麻烦  那也是我的麻烦
With all due respect,
恕我直言
he could become a problem for us all.
他可能会成为我们所有人的麻烦
My husband controls Salem, and I control him.
塞勒姆我丈夫说了算  而他又对我言听计从
You do nothing without my say.
所以我没发话你不许轻举妄动
With all due respect.
无意冒犯
Yes, ma'am.
是  夫人
Concern yourself with one thing, Mr. Hale --
你的任务只有一个  霍尔先生
Find out who broke our circle.
找到破坏祭祀圈的人
Head back to the woods.
再去树林
Find the seer.
找到鬼眼
His eyes were there.
他当时有眼线在场
It was right here we saw the witches.
我们就是在这里看到巫师的
Captain Alden saw all this, too?
奥登上尉也看到了吗
Yeah.
对
And something else...
还有别的...
Something I ain't seen before.
我之前从未见过
They stabbed a bird --
他们刺死了一只鸟
A white dove.
一只白鸽
I killed more than a few pigeons myself,
我自己杀过不少鸽子
and a dove ain't nothing but a prettier pigeon,
白鸽不过就是只好看点的鸽子
but this felt different.
但这次感觉不同
I can't say why...
我也说不上原因
Like it was the saddest thing in the world...
就好像那是世上最悲伤的事
To bleed a dove to death.
让一只白鸽血流至死
Just the one dove.
只是一只白鸽
Of course. Like a witch's cauldron.
果然  就像巫师之釜
A tree? Like a cauldron?
一棵树  像釜
And folks say Isaac's touched.
人们还说我疯了
Got you.
找到了
Mrs. Sibley.
西布里夫人
- Open it. - Yes, ma'am.
-打开  -是  夫人
Now leave.
退下吧
Salem still hangs men for what you did...
你的行为在塞勒姆可是要处以绞刑的
Threatening the selectmen.
你威胁了镇长
Nothing stopping them.
什么都阻止不了他们
I'd never let that happen.
我绝不会让那种事发生的
And where was that compassion
那么吉尔斯·科里被大石压死时
when Giles Corey was being crushed to death?
你那怜悯之心哪去了
You're free to go.
你可以走了
But the selectmen urge you to leave Salem and never come back.
但是镇长要你离开塞勒姆  永不回来
The selectmen...
是镇长要我离开
...or Mary Sibley?
还是玛丽·西布里
I am trying to save you.
我这是在救你
You don't belong here.
你不属于这里
And neither do you.
你也不属于这里
I told you... I can't leave.
我告诉过你了  我不能走
Well, last time I checked,
据我所知
your husband was in no shape to stop you.
你丈夫可没那个本事阻止你
Your confidence astounds me, Captain.
真没想到你如此自信啊  上尉
But did you imagine that I would welcome you back
你是不是一直想象我会满含喜悦的泪水
with tears of joy?
欢迎你回来
How incredibly naive you are.
你真是天真啊
You're too late.
太晚了
It's over.
都结束了
I don't want you here.
我不想在这里看到你
I almost believe you.
我差点就相信你了
Get out of Salem... now...
马上离开塞勒姆
Or you will hang.
否则你会被绞死的
Sir.
先生
All right, you can do this.
加把劲  你可以的
I can't do it.
我做不到
- It's too big. - Yes, you can.
-太大了  -你可以的
I have gotten bigger babies out of smaller girls.
比你小的姑娘都能顺利生下更大的孩子呢
Not this baby out of this girl,
不能让这个姑娘生下孩子
not until she tells us the name of the father.
除非她肯说出孩子父亲的名字
Mrs. Sibley, excuse me,
西布里夫人  恕我直言
but this baby has got to come out.
这孩子必须得生下来
Salem won't shoulder another bastard.
塞勒姆不会接受这个野种
What are you doing here?
你在这里做什么
My friend Bridget teaches me
我的朋友布里奇特在教我
the wonders of God's own creation.
上帝造物的神奇
Hannah,
汉娜
will you tell us the name of your man?
把他的名字说出来好吗
I cannot, miss. He'll lose his apprenticeship.
我不能说  小姐  否则他就当不成学徒了
He ain't allowed to marry for some years yet.
这几年他是不能结婚的
That is his problem, not Salem's.
那是他的问题  不是塞勒姆的
Mary, you're a woman.
玛丽  你也是女人
You were even a poor one once.
也曾穷困潦倒
But now you're Mary Sibley.
但现在你是玛丽·西布里
For once, use your position among the puritans
就一次  用你在清教徒中的地位
to help one of your own.
帮帮自己人吧
No man is worth it, child,
没有男人值得你如此  孩子
or if he is, he would rather you tell us his name
如果他值得  他就宁愿你说出他的名字
than die trying to protect him.
也不要你为保护他而死
Billy!
比利
It was Billy Bailyn, the cooper's apprentice.
是比利·贝林  桶匠的学徒
Just relax. Stay with me.
放轻松  听我说
All right, Hannah.
没事的  汉娜
I want you to give me a big push.
我需要你再用点力
Almost there!
就差一点
That's it.
就这样
Big push. Well done!
用力  很好
Keep going.
继续
That's it.
生出来了
Help me!
救救我
It's going to be all right.
没事的
Excuse us, madam.
抱歉  夫人
Come on, now. In you go.
来吧  进去
Petrus, really.
彼得鲁斯  不是吧
You ought to wear a little bell.
你真该挂个铃铛了
And you, Magistrate, need none.
而您  治安官大人  就大可不必了
We heard you the moment you left the road.
您一上路我们就听到动静了
Come.
来
I had a bit of trouble finding the place.
这地方可真不好找
Seemed to recall you having been farther north last time.
让我记起  上次你还去了更北的地方
Perhaps I was, Magistrate Hale.
也许我真去过  霍尔治安官
Eyes are for seeing,
眼睛是用来洞察
not for being seen.
而不是被发现的
That's why your kind come to me.
这也是你们这种人来找我的原因
You find me when you need me.
需要的时候你就会找到我
So, what do you need?
说吧  这次需要什么
Someone broke our circle in the woods last night.
昨晚我们在树林里的祭祀圈被破坏了
We need to know who saw us.
我们得知道有谁看见了
Full buck moon?
雄鹿满月
You were there that night, weren't you, little friend?
那晚你在场  是吧  小家伙
Time to wake up.
该醒醒了
What did you see?
你看见什么了
Tell Mary Sibley we will find out
告诉玛丽·西布里我们会查清
who was in the woods last night,
昨晚谁在那片树林里
but it takes time.
但需要时间
Lord...
主...
Have our prayers been answered?
我们的祷告有回应了吗
Has the poor girl improved?
这可怜的姑娘好些了吗
We should not be praying for God to do
我们自己能做的事
what we can accomplish ourselves.
不该恳求上帝完成
Mercy Lewis is not suffering the work of witches or demons,
梅西·路易丝所受的折磨并非来自巫师或魔鬼
but some natural malady or fever of the mind,
只是自然疾病  或是头脑发烧了
yet she hangs here like an animal.
可她却被吊在这里  像牲畜一样
She broke her ropes three times at home,
她在家中三次挣脱绳索
not to mention her father's arm.
更不必提她父亲手臂的伤了
She bit off her own finger
她咬断自己的手指
and tears at her flesh.
撕裂自己的血肉
Mercy must be protected from herself and we from her.
必须保护她不能伤害自己和大家
There's no better place to do both than in the house of God.
没有比上帝之所更适合的地方了
I think the selectmen are exploiting her condition
我认为执行官只是利用她的处境
to create fear in Salem.
在塞勒姆制造恐慌
This so-called "witch panic"
这种所谓的"巫师恐慌"
is yet another attempt by the puritans to control us.
只是清教徒试图控制我们的把戏
Miss Bishop, please...
毕谢普小姐  请你...
Be careful of the words that you speak.
请你注意自己的言辞
To less sympathetic ears,
若是让狠心的人听了去
they could sound like the words of the devil himself.
会以为这是魔鬼本人在说话呢
I'm...sorry if my words were harsh.
很抱歉...我失言了
Sometimes, my tongue runs ahead of my mind.
我有时候说话不经大脑
It's understandable.
可以理解
These are trying times for all of us.
这对我们所有人都是种考验
Careful, mistress.
小心点  夫人
Your tears may sour the milk.
你的泪水可能会让乳汁酸腐
There was a time
曾经的我
that I might have suckled something other than a toad.
也能哺育其他生命  而不是蟾蜍
It doesn't matter now.
现在都无关紧要了
What matters is, who will be next?
重要的是  下一个目标是谁
The grand rite has begun,
大祭典已经开始
and the earth cries out for innocent blood.
土地渴求着纯洁鲜血的滋养
I know well my duties.
我很清楚自己的职责
Attend to your own.
顾好你自己吧
Your duties and seeing that you fulfill them
我的职责就是看好你履行职责
is my duty, like it or not.
不管你愿不愿意
I've made my choice.
我已经做出决定了
But we need more than another victim --
但我们需要的不只是祭品
We need a sign.
还需要一个征兆
And I know just the person to deliver us both.
而我正好知道一个人可以同时提供这两者
Our Cotton Mather is quite obsessed with signs --
我们的柯顿·麦哲神父对征兆颇为着迷
wrote chapter and verse on them.
在他的书里时有提起
But there is one sign they dread more than any other.
但有一个征兆比其它的都要可怕
The sign of a monstrous birth.
那就是畸婴出世
You would do such a thing?
你做得出这样的事情吗
No, I have no need
不  根本不需要我
to pluck a single leaf from the tree of life
亲手从生命之树上摘除那片叶子
when a leaf is already dead on the branch.
因为它在枝头便已然枯萎
There's a girl out there
镇里有一个女孩
who carries death inside.
她怀了一个死婴
I could smell the baby,
我能闻到它的气味
floating dead and malformed in her mother's womb.
那个死于母亲腹中的畸形婴儿
Don't weep for her.
无需为她惋惜
She never tasted a single bitter breath of life's betrayals.
至少她永远不会尝到被命运背叛的苦涩
Yet her brief flicker of life
而当我将她作为
will burn like a comet over earth
厄运即将降临塞勒姆的征兆时
when I make of her a sign...
她转瞬即逝的人生
of the doom that's come upon Salem.
将如流星般耀眼
Do you know what I enjoy most, George?
你知道我最享受的是什么吗  乔治
Turning the good souls of Salem against one another,
让塞勒姆的善良人们如你教导的那般
like the rabid dogs you trained them to be.
像疯狗一样自相残杀
The only thing that keeps me alive
我活着就是为了有一天
is the look on your face
能亲眼见到
when John Alden finds out what you really are
当约翰·奥登发现你真正身份时你脸上的表情
and throttles you with his bare han--
看着他亲手勒死你
Just think, George.
别忘了  乔治
I need only kill nine more innocents
我只需要在猎月到来之前
before full hunter's moon,
再杀死九名无辜者
and my grand rite is complete.
我的大祭典就将完成
Shush now, Kitty.
没事的  姬蒂
If lying with old fat Fred didn't kill you,
如果那个老胖子弗雷德在床上都没折腾死你
delivering his child won't, neither.
那生他的孩子也一定不会
No! It feels like it'll tear me in two.
不  它快将我撕成两半了
It's almost time.
是时候了
Go fetch Bridget.
快去叫布里奇特过来
Miss Bridget!
布里奇特小姐
I was just coming to get you.
我正准备去找你
I heard poor Kitty's screams.
我听到她的惨叫了  可怜的姬蒂
Kitty, Kitty, Kitty.
姬蒂  姬蒂
Nothing to fear now.
这下不用怕了
Miss Bridget's seen more babes through the narrow gate than any.
布里奇特小姐丰富的接生经验可是无人能比
Don't fret, child. The baby's just the wrong way 'round.
别害怕孩子  这婴儿只是胎位不正
It is a simple thing to turn it.
纠正过来很容易的
No!
不
No! No! No! No!
不要  不要
She's hurting my baby!
她在伤害我的孩子
You witnessed a real witches' sabbat --
你亲眼见证了巫师集会
Something no witch hunter
这是任何巫师猎手
has ever seen with his own eyes.
至今都没有机会亲眼见证的
All of our images and accounts come from confessions,
所有的图像与描述都源于人们的忏悔
some...rather more believable than others.
只能说  当中有些并不十分可信
It's this one.
就是这个
If this is true, it's far worse than I thought.
如果这是真的  那情况比我想象的更加严重
What's it say?
上面说的什么
No Latin, captain?
不认识拉丁文吗  上尉
Oh, of course not. You've no time for books.
当然了  你无暇阅读书籍
"Ritum Magni."
"伟大的仪式"
The Grand Rite --
大祭典
The greatest secret of the witches.
巫师们最大的秘密
All we have are scraps of rumors of failed attempts.
目前我们只听说过数次失败尝试的传言
Unfortunately, there are no books by witches --
不幸的是  巫师们从不写书
only witch hunters.
只有巫师猎手写的
So all of these books...
所以说  这么多书
tell you exactly nothing.
实际上一无所用
Stop it.
住手
You fight each other.
如果你们互相争斗
Who fights them?
那谁去对抗他们
He has a point.
他说得有理
So, where do we begin?
那么  我们从何入手
Inside the tree, I found what fuels their work...
在那棵树中  我发现了他们汲取能量的来源
like the wood of a fire.
正如生火需要的薪柴一般
See, everything the witch does is powered by two things --
巫师们的一切巫术都需要两样东西提供能量
Lust and death.
肉欲与死亡
The lust they provide for themselves,
她们可以靠自身获得肉欲
but they must look elsewhere for the dead parts.
但必须从别处获得死亡
The town would be aware if their own Salem burial ground
如果塞勒姆的墓地被人破坏的话
was being disturbed by corpse grinding.
镇里的人们一定会发现的
So where do they get them?
那他们要从哪得到它
Isaac, if you'd be so kind
艾萨克  你能好心
as to explain to the captain your duties.
向上尉解释下你的工作吗
I got all kind of duties --
我有各种工作
Packages to deliver.
比如说运送包裹
I also deliver the unwanteds to the crags.
我还负责将被遗弃者运去山壑
The unwanteds?
被遗弃者
You know, Indians, slaves, criminals --
你知道的  印第安人  奴隶  还有罪犯
pretty much anybody ain't fit to be laid in salem ground.
就是那些没有资格葬在塞勒姆墓地的人
This is where the witches harvest.
那就是巫师们收获能量的地方
And at the risk of another thrashing,
尽管这么说可能会再次挑起你的怒火
it is also your best hope
但在那里
of reclaiming your friend's remains.
你才能取回你朋友的尸骨
You dumped his body into the crags?!
你将他的尸体丢进了山壑
Giles Corey built half this town,
半个小镇都是吉尔斯·科里一手建起来的
And you threw him into a goddamn ditch?!
你却把他丢在一条破水沟里吗
Let's go.
咱们走
Where?
去哪
To get Giles out of that shithole.
去带吉尔斯离开那个鬼地方
All of salem is diminished by your loss.
整个塞勒姆都为你的损失感到悲痛
I can only imagine your suffering.
我无法想象你有多么痛苦
Thank you, Mrs. Sibley.
谢谢您  西布里夫人
The others said that you were frightened...
他们说你很害怕
You thought that someone was trying to hurt your baby?
你以为有人想害你的孩子
Tell me what happened.
跟我说说怎么回事
Tell me.
说吧
I'm going to tell you something.
我先告诉你一些事
I've never told anyone before.
我从来没告诉过任何人
I, too, have lost a child.
我也失去过一个孩子
Oh, I know the pain you feel.
我了解你那种痛楚
I feel it even now.
时至今日  我仍心如刀绞
You must tell me what happened
你一定得告诉我发生了什么
So that your child did not die in vain.
这样你的孩子才不会白白死去
I promise you...
我向你保证
No harm will come to you.
不会有人伤害你的
Tell me.
告诉我吧
I felt the presence of evil...
我感觉到了恶魔的存在
And...
并且...
Go on.
继续说
...I saw a foul hag.
我看到了一个邪恶的女巫
And she was touching my belly.
她抚摸着我的肚子
What of the midwife?
那助产士呢
What of her?
她怎么了
They were one and the same.
她们是同一个人
Two times in as many nights?
一天来两次  还是晚上
Two times too many.
这鬼地方根本不是人该来的
Show me where you dumped his body.
带路  你把他的尸体扔哪了
Jesus Christ.
天啊
Where is he?
他在哪
There.
那边
You do not lay a hand on that man.
别拿你的脏手碰他
Oh, forgive me.
抱歉
Ordinarily, this would be George's domain,
正常情况下应该是乔治来的
But my husband... his condition...
但我丈夫...他的情况...
I fear that the very sight of this would stop his heart.
这东西我怕他只看一眼都会心脏骤停
Mrs. Sibley, please...
西布里夫人
Calm yourself.
请冷静
What is wrong?
怎么了
Oh, a most terrible thing...
最糟糕的事情发生了
A sign.
一个征兆
A sign?
征兆
Yes, just as you described in one of your books.
没错  就像你书里描述的一样
A monstrous birth.
畸婴出世
What?
什么
Here in salem?
在塞勒姆吗
Delivered by our very own midwife...
由我们的助产士亲手接生
Bridget Bishop.
布里奇特·毕谢普
And where is ...
这个...
What has become of this monster now?
这个怪物现在在哪
Where is it?
它在哪
In this very room.
就在这个房间里
Mr. Lamb floated it in a bottle. I...
兰姆先生把它泡在了一个瓶子里  我...
By the wounds of Christ!
多苦多难的上帝啊
The mere sight of this would
这景象  哪怕只是一瞥
pierce our dear lord yet again!
便足以再次狠狠伤害他
You were right to send for me.
您找我来是对的
This is most terrible.
这真是太恐怖了
But what does it portend?
这预示着什么
What is this a sign of?
这是什么征兆
There can be no doubt.
毫无疑问
'tis nothing less than a declaration of war upon us
这一切就是魔鬼本人
by the devil himself.
在向我们宣战
Reverend...
牧师
Is there anything we can do?
我们能做什么吗
I will do whatever is in my power
我会竭尽所能
to protect Salem...
保护塞勒姆
and you, madam.
和您  夫人
I thank God you're here, reverend.
感谢上帝你在这里  牧师
We would be lost without you.
若没有你  我们真不知如何是好了
Father, please wait.
父亲  请等等
Father, you know Bridget.
父亲  您认识布里奇特
How could you think her guilty of this?
您怎能认为她犯下了这种罪孽
It isn't a matter of what I think.
我怎么认为无关紧要
Father.
父亲
Another rush to judgment, Mather?
又一次草率的审判吗  麦哲
Quite the contrary, I fear.
恐怕正相反
It is judgment that is rushing towards all of us.
是上帝的最后审判正在向我们逼近
Behold the warrant of judgment.
请看证据
For our sins, individual and collective,
无论是个人  还是我们共同的罪恶
he has signed the seal of Satan,
他代表着撒旦的印记
a message straight from hell
一个来自地狱的讯息
to herald the arrival of the devil in Salem.
宣告着恶魔在塞勒姆的降临
And who delivered his message for him?
那么是谁为他传达的信息呢
Bridget Bishop.
布里奇特·毕谢普
Did you or did you not
你是否
deliver this monster from that girl?
从那女孩身体里接生了这个怪物
Yes, but..
是的  可是...
Did you or did you not
你是否
minister to this girl while she carried it?
在她带孕期间一直照料着她
Yes, sir, but I minister...
是的先生  可我照顾...
Did you or did you not
你是否
Frequently dose her with physics and potions
时常喂她服食一些药品和药剂
and herbal concoctions of your own devising?
和自制的混合草药汤给她服用
Sir, that is what I do, but I did not --
先生  是我做的  但是我没有
And did you or did you not place your hands upon her belly,
你有没有把你的手放在她的肚子上
pressing this way and that
如此这般按压
just before the thing came out?
就在它出来之前
I was turning the babe so --
我在变化胎儿的位...
Aye, but turning it into what?
没错  把胎儿变成了什么
Stop!
够了
Whatever that poor stone child may be,
不管那个石婴是什么
you are the true monster!
你才是真正的怪物
I apologize for my daughter.
我为小女道歉
The accused is a dear friend of hers.
被告是她的亲密好友
But I share her concern.
不过我和她持有同样的疑惑
You would accuse a woman --
你指控的是一个
a woman whom we all know and trust,
我们都熟悉并信赖
who never did anything but help other women
一心帮助其他妇女
to deliver their babies
为她们接生
and care for those who no one wanted?
照料弃婴的女人
And now, suddenly, we're to believe she's a witch?
现在突然要我们相信她是个女巫吗
The devil is patient.
恶魔很耐心
And so are his servants --
它的仆人也是如此
our friends, our neighbors --
可能是我们的朋友  可能是邻居
Till, finally, they are called to serve him.
直到恶魔召唤他们来服侍
Bridget Bishop,
布里奇特·毕谢普
You have delivered a monster into the world.
你助畸婴出世
You were seen in your true guise,
被受害者看穿了你的真正面目
the night hag, by your victim.
一个邪恶的老巫婆
And even those who were duped by your innocent image
就算是那些曾经被你无辜形象蒙骗的人们
could still sense the palpable stench of evil around them,
仍然能感受到明显的恶魔阴影围绕着他们
as you destroyed
因为你毁灭了
a babe in the cradle of life --
一个未出生的婴儿
a sign of your master's declaration of war upon us.
这是你的主人向我们宣战的征兆
How do you plead?
你认罪吗
I did no such thing.
我没做过这样的事
I'm innocent!
我是无辜的
Oh, you must belive me -- I am --
您得相信我  我
I'm a little confused, Mather.
我有点困惑  麦哲
Did Bridget make that sign...
是布里奇特制造了那个征兆
or did God?
还是上帝
No. No, no, no. Wait. I remember.
不对  等等  我记起来了
God told the devil, and the devil made her do it --
上帝告知恶魔  恶魔迫使她这么做
have I got this right?
我说的对不对
No? Maybe I'm just not as smart as you.
不对吗  可能是我没有你那么聪明
I haven't read all those books,
我虽不像你读过那么多书
but I have seen a few things in the world.
但我也算见识了不少市面
And in this world, bad things happen,
在这个世界上  坏事时有发生
generally with no more meaning than the roll of a dice.
如同掷骰子一般  并说明不了什么
This monstrosity --
这个怪物
it's just an unlucky roll of god's dice?
只是上帝掷的一次不幸的骰子吗
Probably the unluckiest I've seen.
可能是我见过最不幸的一次
Well, then, we have a most profound difference of opinion.
那我们的想法真是非常不同
We do.
确实
But you would hang a woman on your opinion.
但是你只根据你的想法就要绞死一个女人
And on yours, you would let an agent of the devil himself
那根据你的想法  就任由恶魔的使徒
walk free to do more malice.
横行并犯下更多罪过吗
Then put her on trial, too.
那你也得审问她
Don't just stop there.
不能只审一人就完事
There were others with her.
她们当时都在场
Or maybe they're all responsible.
可能她们都有责任
No, you can't! It's not my fault!
不行  你不能这样  不是我的错
It's not your fault?
不是你的错吗
No, I think that you're probably right.
不  我想你可能说得对
I think -- and I know this is unthinkable to you, Mather --
我知道对你来说难以置信  麦哲
But maybe, just maybe, it's no one's fault.
但是可能  这不是任何人的错
We all know that killing is different.
而我们都知道  杀人不同
Killing is always someone's fault.
杀人一定有肇事者
The stones aren't dry from the blood of Giles Corey,
吉尔斯·科里尸骨未寒
And now you are willing to hang a woman --
现在你又要绞死一个女人
This woman, bridget bishop --
这个女人  布里奇特·毕谢普
and, hell, throw in a few whores for good measure --
或许再加上几个妓女
and for what?
这都为了什么
Perhaps it's time we heard from Mercy.
或许我们该听听梅西怎么说
Isn't that right, reverend Mather?
不对吗  麦哲牧师
Isn't she bound to react
她不是一定会
in front of the guilty witch or witches?
在有罪的巫师面前有所反应的吗
My father and all the experts agree --
我父亲和所有专家同意
Then take them to her.
那就将她们带到她面前
Them?
她们
Captain Alden is quite right.
奥登上尉说得很对
All may be guilty.
所有人都可能有罪
Take the midwife and the three whores, too.
把助产士和三个妓女带到她面前
Shall we vote?
可以投票了吗
Lord...
主啊
You who sees and knows our secret hearts
您知晓我们不为人知的内心
must know that I am innocent.
您一定知道我是无辜的
Please, please, please give them
拜托  拜托  拜托  请给他们
some visible sign of this simple truth.
一些启示  揭露这个简单的真相
Please.
求求您
Well done.
干得好
Another innocent killed.
你又杀了一个无辜的人
I do not think so.
我不这么认为
But even if I did...
即便我真的滥杀了无辜
let the lord add it
就让主把这个
to my already lengthy list of mortal sins.
也加入我那已经长长的罪恶清单上去吧
I must pay any price,
我必须不惜一切代价
spill my own or any other's blood to stop the witches.
撒上我自己或他人的血都要阻止那些巫师
I don't think I've ever seen such a mixture
我还从来没见过这样一位
of reason and bullshit in a man.
集理智与狗屎于一身的人
If you only knew what I know...
如果你能知我所知
What?
怎样
I'd crush a man or hang a woman,
我就会压死一个男人  吊死个女人
then drink myself blind
喝个酩酊大醉
and bury myself into a whore like there's no tomorrow?
然后跟妓女翻云覆雨  誓死方休吗
If we do not stop these foul hags,
如果我们不阻止这些邪恶的女巫
there will be no tomorr--
那我们就不会有明...
You monster!
你个禽兽
Stop!
住手
What a mess you've made of things.
看你把事情搞得多乱
We were nearly ruined by a single sound argument
就因为你放不下那个男人
from a man you can't seem to let alone.
我们差点被他那通反驳坏了大事
I question now why we let you begin this.
我开始质疑为何让你这么做
Why?
为什么
Because this is the fulfillment of all our dreams --
因为这是我们所有人的梦想
vengeance for centuries of oppression.
报复几个世纪以来的镇压
Too late for doubts now, Hale.
现在动摇太晚了  霍尔
We are all in this together.
咱们已经是一股绳子上的了
Yes, and we shall all burn together at this rate.
是啊  这样下去咱们定会一起被烧死
You're too young to understand the risk you're taking.
你太年轻了  不理解你所经受的风险
I saw my entire family burned at the stake.
我看着我全家人烧死在柱子上
I tasted their ashes in my mouth.
我亲口尝到了他们骨灰的味道
I have no desire to taste my own...
我没有兴趣去品尝我自己的
or my daughter's.
亦或是我女儿的
Well, perhaps you old-world witches
也许你们这些旧世界巫师
are simply too scared
只是过于胆怯
or too scarred to claim this new world.
没有魄力去统治这个新世界
Not me.
但我不会
I'm not alone.
我不是一个人
The elders have their doubts, too.
元老们也心有动摇
All your fears are unnecessary.
你的恐惧完全没有必要
Innocent blood flows and will continue to flow.
无辜之血将继续流淌
Results, Mr. Hale, are all that matter.
结果  霍尔先生  那才是最重要的
And speaking of results,
而说到结果
What of your errand?
你该做的事进行得如何了
Petrus assures us we'll soon know who saw us.
彼得鲁斯说很快就会找出目击者
Oh, um...sorry, Miss Hale,
抱歉  霍尔小姐
But, uh, you know the rules.
但是  你知道规矩的
There's, uh,
这个
no women allowed after dark.
女人天黑后禁止入内
It's all right, Lamb.
没事的  兰博
According to Mather, these are the end times.
据麦哲说  终结即将来临
I think we can make an exception for tonight.
我想今晚可以开个特例
What are you looking at?
你在看什么
You're just like them --
你和他们一样
happy to discuss and debate,
喜欢高谈阔论  唇枪舌剑
but too afraid to take any real action.
却从不敢真正行动起来
Why are you even in Salem?
你还在塞勒姆干什么
Where's that fire I saw in your eyes
他们杀死你朋友那晚
the night they killed your friend?
我在你眼中看到的怒火去哪了
What do you want from me, Miss Hale?
你想让我干什么  霍尔小姐
Justice --
正义
for Giles Corey, for Bridget Bishop,
为吉尔斯·科里  为布里奇特·毕谢普
and for all the other innocent victims
还为了这场即将到来的混乱中
soon to come from this madness.
更多的无辜受害者们
Someone must do something!
必须有人来做些什么
What?
怎么了
You just remind me of someone I once knew.
你让我想起了曾经认识的一个人
What happened to them?
他们怎么了
I wish I knew.
真希望我能知道
Here uninvited --
不请自来
You must have stayed too long with the indians.
你一定是和印第安人呆太久了
It's made you more...
让你变得更像...
savage.
野蛮人了
No. Less patient.
不  只是更没有耐心而已
There's something I think you should know.
有些事我认为你需要知道
You're leaving Salem?
你要离开塞勒姆
To the contrary.
正相反
Anne Hale reminded me Salem deserves better.
安·霍尔提醒了我塞勒姆不应如此
It always did.
该做出些改变了
Really?
真的
I thought you hated this place.
我还以为你厌恶这地方
I thought so, too.
我本也这么想
But it turns out it wasn't Salem that I hated --
但结果发现我恨的不是塞勒姆
Rather, the people who run it.
而是控制他的那些人
Fella told me something today --
今天有人和我说了一些事情
he said it was a damn sight easier
他说这种景象
to break things than to fix them.
破坏比修复要简单得多
And you intend to fix things.
而你想要来进行修复
Maybe.
也许吧
How do you plan on doing that?
你准备怎么做
There's an extra seat on the board of selectmen --
行政委员的位子还空着一个
a seat with the Alden name.
一个属于奥登家族的位子
Reckoned maybe it was time I claimed it.
也许是时候我来接手了
Might just be one voice,
一个人的声音尽管微弱
but it is a start.
但这是个开始
I'll be seeing you.
我们还会再见的
Go away, cat.
走开  猫咪
You'll ruin my work.
你会弄坏我作品的